PRIVACY STATEMENT

This Privacy Statement covers the information practices of Hertz Car Sales, LLC and its applicable car sales subsidiaries and affiliates whose registered office is 8501 Williams Road Estero, Florida 33928 ("Hertz") and is to be read in conjunction with the The Hertz Corporation Privacy Policy which can be found [here](https://www.hertz.com/rentacar/privacypolicy/index.jsp?&targetPage=privacyPolicyView.jsp). This Privacy Statement was last updated December 31, 2019.

Hertz believes strongly in protecting your privacy and the confidentiality of your Personal Information. We acknowledge that you may have privacy and security concerns with respect to the information we collect, use, and disclose to third parties for the purpose of allowing us to view and/or sell our vehicles and            services to you. As used in this Statement, Personal Information is any combination of information, in the possession of or likely to come into the possession of Hertz, that identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular individual or household ("Personal  Information")  and  will  be  treated  in  accordance  with  this  Privacy Statement. Any information which cannot be used to identify a discrete individual or household (such as aggregated statistical information) is not Personal Information.

PURPOSE FOR COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Hertz collects, uses and discloses your Personal Information in its normal course of business for the following purposes:

·         Where you are interested in purchasing a vehicle from Hertz, assisting you in the completion of your application and the assessment of your eligibility for making such a purchase;

·         Where you have purchased a vehicle from Hertz, the processing and maintenance of any additional services you have obtained with the purchased vehicle, as well as any applicable renewal of such service;

·         Establishing and maintaining communications with you;

·         Responding to your inquiries about other vehicles or services;

·         Allowing our affiliated companies to notify you of certain vehicles, products, or services offered by our affiliated companies;

·         Processing transactions through service providers (e.g. banks);

·         Meeting legal, security, processing, and regulatory requirements;

·         Protecting against fraud, suspicious or other illegal activities.

WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

The information gathered by Hertz during the initial interest and/or purchasing process falls into two categories: (1) information voluntarily supplied you and (2) information provided by third parties necessary to complete any sales transaction.

Information voluntarily provided by you
=======================================

When purchasing or viewing a vehicle, you may choose to provide us with information to help us serve your needs. The Personal Information that we collect will depend on what those needs are.

·         Where and what type of vehicle you are looking to purchase

To best provide you with a positive experience, we may collect information about your preferences and needs in a vehicle. We may use this information to communicate with you in the future regarding such preferred vehicle. We may also collect information related to any additional services which go along with purchasing such a vehicle. For example, we may collect information related to your financing needs, your warranty or servicing needs, and other services       which are offered with the vehicle by third parties (like OnStar subscriptions, SIRIUSXM subscriptions or AT&T in-vehicle hot-spot services). If you request further information about third party services, we require you to submit your name, e-mail address, and other Personal Information so we may send you the material you have requested, and to enable us to support the third party offering those services to you.

Any Personal Information that you send us will be used for the purpose indicated this Privacy Statement or as otherwise necessary for the completion of the sales transaction you agree to.

Information provided by Third Parties
=====================================

As part of your purchase of a vehicle from Hertz, we may be required to collect information from third parties such as governmental or taxing authorities. Additionally, we may be required to check your credit history if you are contemplating financing your purchase of a vehicle. As a consequence, we will also collect information from consumer reporting agencies relating to your credit and insurability.

DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO OTHERS

We do not disclose any Personal Information about you to any third parties except as stated in this Privacy Statement, as otherwise permitted by law, or authorized by you. We may sell or otherwise monetize your information to unrelated third parties where permitted by law.

Third parties to whom we disclose information are required by law and contractual undertakings to keep your Personal Information confidential and secure, and to use and disclose it for purposes that a reasonable person would consider appropriate in the circumstances, in compliance with all applicable legislation, which purposes are as follows:

·         To provide the products and services you have requested from us;

·         To notify you or allow our entrusted third parties to notify you of certain products or services offered by our entrusted third parties;

·         For legal, claims settlement and valuation services;

·         To process transactions through data processing service providers;

·         If the information is a credit card number, to process credit card payments-through third party payment processing, clearing and settlement systems in association with various banks; and

·         To other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements.

If these third parties wish to use your Personal Information for any other purpose, they will have a legal obligation to notify you of this and, where required, to obtain your consent. Contact us at [Privacy@Hertz.com](mailto:Privacy@Hertz.com) for more information on these third parties.

Affiliate Sharing

In the normal course of performing services for our clients, Personal Information may be shared within Hertz and its affiliates for marketing, research and statistical purposes, system administration, and crime prevention or detection.

Service Providers

Hertz vehicles often have services which correspond or are otherwise available to the owner of the vehicle. For example, warranty, road-side services, and     mobile communication services may be available for the vehicle you are purchasing. In order to best support your acquisition and use of such services, your Personal Information may be disclosed to these service providers as part of your transaction with Hertz.

Additionally, Hertz may engage other third party service providers in support of our interaction with you. We will provide relevant personal Information to these service providers as well. Hertz's service suppliers adhere to the same protections regarding the collection, use, and retention of data as we do.

Business Transactions

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, user information, including Personal Information, generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, if either Hertz itself or substantially all of Hertz assets were acquired, your Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets. Therefore, we may disclose and/or transfer your Personal Information to a third party purchaser in these circumstances

Other Legally Required Disclosures

Hertz preserves the right to disclose, without your prior permission, any Personal Information about you if Hertz has a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) protect and defend the rights, property or safety of Hertz, employees, other customers or clients, or the public; (b) enforce the terms and conditions that apply to the purchase of a vehicle; or (c) as required by a legally valid request from a competent governmental authority. We may also disclose Personal Information as we deem necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request

LIMITING COLLECTION AND RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Hertz will collect, use, or disclose Personal Information that is necessary for the purposes described in this Statement or as permitted by law.

Hertz will collect Personal Information by fair and lawful means. We will normally retain Personal Information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of the Identified Purposes. However, some Personal Information may be retained for longer periods as required by law, contract, or auditing requirements.

SAFEGUARDS

We have in place physical, electronic and procedural safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information we maintain. Safeguards will vary depending on the sensitivity, format, location, amount, distribution and storage of the Personal Information. They include physical, technical, and managerial measures to keep Personal Information protected from unauthorized access

ACCURACY, ACCOUNTABILITY, OPENNESS AND CUSTOMER ACCESS

Our knowing about changes to some of your Personal Information (e.g. email address) may be key to effectively communicating with you at your request. If any of your details change you can update us by e-mailing us at [contact@Hertz.com.](mailto:contact@Hertz.com) Please keep us informed of changes to your Personal Information.

CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

California's Civil Code section 1798.100 et seq. provides residents of California a number of rights as they relate to Personal Information. These are the "right to know", the "right to delete", and the "right to opt-out".

Right to Know. You may request Hertz provide you the specific pieces of personal information that Hertz has about you; categories of personal information we have collected about you; categories of sources from which the personal information is collected; categories of personal information that Hertz sold or disclosed for a business purpose about you; categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold or disclosed for a business purpose; and the business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling personal information. Please note that much of the information you can make a request for is already contained in this Policy. Should you wish to exercise this right, please see the section below which explains how to do so. If you do not have an account with Hertz, we may ask for some Personal Information in order to verify your identity and your rights to the data subject to your request.

Right to Delete. California law gives residents a limited right to request deletion of their Personal Information. However, this right is limited by a number of exceptions. Fundamentally, if Hertz has a permissible need to retain Personal Information, we are not under an obligation to delete such information, even when requested. Generally, we retain Personal Information so we may complete the transaction for which the personal information was collected, provide a good or service requested by you, or reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform a contract between us and you; detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity; or prosecute those responsible for that activity; debug to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality of our online properties; enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with your expectations based on your relationship with Hertz; comply with a legal obligation; or otherwise use your personal information, internally, in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which your provided the information. As such, we generally do not accept requests to delete Personal Information. However, we will respond to requests to remove Personal Information from some of our systems as a part of a request to close or otherwise disable a membership account. If you would like to request deletion of Personal Information, please see the section below which explains how to do so. If you do not have an account with Hertz, we may ask for some Personal Information in order to verify your identity and your rights to the data subject to your request.

Right to Opt-Out. We may sell or otherwise monetize your information to unrelated third parties where permitted by law. You have the right to request that We do not sell Personal Information that We have collected.  If you exercise that right, please note that pursuant to the CCPA We may have to subsequently inform you that you need to opt-in if the sale of your Personal Information is required to complete a transaction you have initiated.  If opting-in is required, We will provide you with the necessary instructions. If you would like to request that We do not sell your Personal Information pursuant to the requirements of the CCPA, click [here](http://www.hertz.com/californiaprivacyrights) or call 888-777-5870.  The link will take you to an interactive webform that you can complete and submit to make a request for deletion; if you use the telephone number, you will be guided through a process that will allow you to submit a request. We may also share Personal Information with third parties for marketing purposes. You may choose to opt-out of the sharing of your Personal Information with third parties for marketing purposes at any time by submitting a request in writing to Our contact address below . Please note that this opt-out does not prohibit disclosure made for non-marketing purposes.

Designating an Authorized Agent. California law permits California residents to designate an agent to manage their rights under California law. If you would like to designate an agent to manage your privacy preferences, you may do so using the mechanisms noted below under "Exercising California Privacy Rights". Note that If you do not have an account with Hertz, we may ask for some Personal Information in order to verify your identity and your rights to the data subject to your request. We will also need sufficient Personal Information about your authorized agent to be able to identify them. As part of this process, you must have permission from your authorized agent to disclose their Personal Information to us for the purpose of acting as your agent.

Non-discrimination. California law does not permit Hertz to discriminate against you because you exercised any your rights under this title, including, but not limited to, by: denying you access to goods or services; charging different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties; providing a different level or quality of goods or services; suggesting that you will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.         

Exercising California privacy rights. If you are a California resident and would like to exercise any of your rights you may do so by going to our website at www.hertz.com/californiaprivacyrights, emailing us at privacy@hertz.com, or calling 888-777-5870.

QUESTIONS OR TO WITHDRAW CONSENTIf you have any further questions about this Statement, or other data handling practices of Hertz, please contact by sending an email to us at: [privacy@Hertz.com](mailto:privacy@Hertz.com)

We will need to validate the identity of anyone making such a request to ensure that we do not provide your information to anyone who does not have the right to such information. Normally we will respond to access requests within 30 days.

\* Indicates a required field

#### Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights

You may exercise your access, data portability, and deletion rights described above by either:

* **Calling us**
* **Completing and submitting the form below**

Privacy
=======

Region\* Please Select California

Nature of Request\* Please Select I want to know what you know about me I want to opt-out of the sale of my data I want my information deleted I want to correct my information I want to opt-out of behavioral advertising/targeted advertising I want to opt-out of use of sensitive data I want to opt-in to use of sensitive data

Incorrect Information\*

Corrected Information\*

First Name\* 

Last Name\* 

Email\* 

Phone\* 

Address\* 

Postal Code\* 

Submit
